http://www.nabihq.org/en-us/terms_and_conditions/

About UsAdminAssociate MembersCons And ScamsContact UsDonateElder ExploitationLaw Enforcement MembersLinksMembersNABI ApplicationNABI StorePrivacy PolicySeminars, Training, And ConferencesTerms And ConditionsTerms And Conditions Home
Terms And Conditions Home
1. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS THROUGH USE
By using the NABI website, you signify your knowledge and acceptance of all terms set forth below (the "Terms of Use"), as well as the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, please do not use the NABI website. We reserve the right, at our discretion and without prior notice, to revise the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Please check the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the NABI website following the posting of any changes to the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.
2. ACCURACY OF INFORMATION
Although every reasonable effort is made to ensure the accuracy of information presented herein, errors may occur and such information should be verified before any action is taken.
3. SITE CONTENT
Except as otherwise noted, all materials contained in the NABI website, including without limitation all images, text, software, illustrations, designs, logos, icons, video and audio content, products and services available on or through the website, and other materials and items, as well as each website as a whole (collectively the "Contents"), are owned, controlled and/or licensed by NABI. The Contents are protected by trademark, trade dress, copyright, and/or other intellectual property rights of NABI or third-party licensors against any unauthorized uses not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use. All worldwide rights, titles and interests in and to the Contents are owned by NABI or third party licensors.
The NABI website and the Contents are intended solely for your information. You may copy or download the Contents for your personal use only, provided that (i) you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices, (ii) you make no modifications to any Contents, (iii) you do not use any Contents materials in a manner that suggests an association with any NABI facility, event, product, service, or brand, and (iv) you do not download quantities of Contents to a database that can be used to avoid future downloads from any NABI website. Otherwise, you may not copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, distribute, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the NABI website, or any related software without NABI's prior written consent. Any use of the Contents on any non-NABI website or computer environment is strictly prohibited. In the event you download software from any NABI website, the software, including any files, images, or data accompanying, incorporated in or generated by the software (collectively, the "Software"), are licensed to you for your personal, noncommercial use only. We do not transfer title to the Software or any other materials on the NABI website to you. You may not redistribute, sell, de-compile, reverse engineer, disassemble, modify, or otherwise reduce the Software to a human-readable form.
4. LAWFUL USE
You agree to use the NABI website and the Contents for lawful purposes only. For example, you agree not to post on or transmit through the NABI website or its discussion board any material which: violates or infringes in any way upon the rights of others; is threatening, abusive or harassing; is defamatory; is invasive of privacy or publicity rights; is obscene or otherwise objectionable; or encourages conduct that would violate any law or give rise to civil or criminal liability. You agree to abide by the Terms of Use and any additional terms or conditions imposed by NABI or any third-party content providers in connection with the Contents or any other third-party content, software or services available on or through any NABI website. You agree not to use the NABI website as to damage, disable, overburden or impair the NABI website or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of the NABI website. You also agree not to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the NABI website; and you agree not to disseminate any information, the dissemination of which would be in violation of any law or regulation.
THE RELEASE OF ANY INFORMATION WHICH IS IN VIOLATION OF LAW OR REGULATION WILL RESULT IN THE FILING OF A CRIMINAL COMPLAINT WITH THE LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCY WITH JURISDICTION OVER THE ACT.
5. DISCLAIMER
YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEBSITE AND THE CONTENTS, WHICH ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS FOR YOUR PERSONAL, NON-COMMERCIAL USE. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NONINFRINGEMENT, AND SECURITY OR CONFIDENTIALITY OF USE OR INFORMATION. WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES REGARDING THIS WEBSITE OR THE CONTENTS, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE AVAILABILITY OF THIS WEBSITE, ANY CORRECTIVE EFFORTS FOR ANY DEFECTS OR ERRORS ON OR IN THE WEBSITE, THE ABSENCE OF ANY VIRUSES, BUGS OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, OR THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE CONTENTS. COSTS ASSOCIATED WITH ANY SERVICING, REPAIR, OR CORRECTION ASSOCIATED IN ANY WAY WITH ANY USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR THE CONTENTS ARE YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY. BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO RELEASE AND HOLD , ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS HARMLESS FROM ALL CLAIMS, ACTIONS, SUITS, AND PROCEEDINGS ARISING FROM THE WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY CLAIM BASED ON DEFAMATION OR MISREPRESENTATION.
Goods or services neither manufactured nor rendered by NABI are the sole responsibility of the manufacturer or provider of those goods or services. We disclaim all warranties and responsibility for those goods and services. The NABI website may contain links to website controlled by parties other than NABI. Those links are provided for your convenience only; we disclaim NABI all warranties and responsibility for those websites, and for the accuracy, availability, or completeness of any content found therein. We make no representations or warranties as to the security of any information (including without limitation credit card and other personal information) you might be requested to give any third party, and you hereby irrevocably waive any claim against NABI with respect to such website and third-party content.
6. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL NABI OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, LICENSORS, SPONSORS, OR PROMOTIONAL PARTNERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS, DAMAGE (WHETHER PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL), INJURY, CLAIM, LIABILITY OR OTHER CAUSE OF ANY KIND RESULTING FROM OR IN ANY WAY ASSOCIATED WITH THIS OR ANY OTHER WEBSITE, THE CONTENTS, ANY LINKED WEBSITE, OR ANY USE THEREOF. THIS LIMITATION APPLIES TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY ANY APPLICABLE LAW AND WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF NABI HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
7. CREDIT CARDS
NABI takes the issue of your privacy seriously. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming a donation. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. Otherwise, we do not share your credit card information with anyone else. To protect the security of your credit card information, we employ the industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. For more information, please read our Privacy Policy.
8. INTERNATIONAL USE
NABI makes no representation that the NABI website or the Contents are appropriate or available for use in locations outside the United States. If you use any NABI website or Contents from a location other than the United States, you are solely responsible for compliance with all applicable local laws, including without limitation any import and export regulations.
9. CHOICE OF LAW AND FORUM
These Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida, USA, excluding its conflicts of law rules. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising from or relating in any way to these Terms of Use, the NABI website and Contents, or your use thereof shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the Ninth Judicial Circuit in the State of Florida. You also agree and submit to the exercise of personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purpose of litigating any such claim or action, and consent to extra-territorial service of process. This Agreement shall be interpreted according to its express terms, with no presumptions against the drafting party.
10. SUBMISSIONS
We are pleased to hear from our visitors and welcome your comments regarding this website. Unfortunately, however, our policy does not allow us to accept or consider creative or original ideas, suggestions, or materials other than those that we have specifically requested. We hope you will understand that the intent of this policy is to avoid the possibility of misunderstandings when projects developed by our professional staff might seem to others to be similar to their own creative work. Please do not send us any unsolicited materials such as ideas, artwork or photos. While we do value your feedback on our services and products, we request that you be specific in your comments on those services and products, and not submit any creative ideas, suggestions, or materials (unless specifically requested by us).
If, at our request, you send certain submissions (such as postings to chat boards, or contest entries) or, despite our request, you send us creative suggestions, ideas, notes, drawings, concepts, or other information (collectively, the "Submissions"), the Submissions shall be deemed, and shall remain, our property. No Submission shall be subject to any obligation of confidence on our part and we shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of any Submissions. Without limitation of the foregoing, we shall exclusively own all now-known or hereafter existing rights to the Submissions of every kind and nature throughout the universe and shall be entitled to unrestricted use of the Submissions for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, without compensation to the provider of the Submissions.
By posting or submitting content to this website, you (1) grant NABI and its affiliates and licensees the right to use, reproduce, display, perform, adapt, modify, distribute, have distributed, and promote the content in any form, anywhere and for any purpose; and (2) warrant and represent that public posting and use of that content by NABI will not infringe or violate the rights of any third party.
11. INDEMNIFICATION
Upon request by NABI, you agree to release and defend, indemnify, and hold harmless NABI and its subsidiary and other affiliated organizations, and their employees, contractors, officers, and directors from and against all liabilities, claims, and expenses, including attorney's fees, that arise from your violation of this Agreement or your use of any NABI website other than as permitted herein. NABI reserves the right, at it own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will cooperate with NABI in asserting any available defenses.
12. SEVERABILITY AND INTEGRATION
Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and NABI with respect to the NABI website and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals (whether oral, written, or electronic) between you and NABI with respect to the NABI website. If any part of these Terms of Use is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.
13. TERMINATION
NABI reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access and license to all or part of this website, with or without notice.
14. Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our terms and conditions, the practices of this website or your dealings with it, you can contact: info@nabihq.org.
This policy was last reviewed on October 28, 2016.
P.O. Box 620087, Oviedo, FL 32762-0087Fax 407-366-0576, email inquiries: inquiry@nabihq.org
Powered by Sacoiwa
Copyright © 2005-2020 The National Association of Bunco Investigators, Inc.All rights reserved worldwide.
Login
UsernamePlease use only lower case a-z, 0-9, @, period and underscore.Password
Always log me in on this computer.
